<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on measured.</title>
    <link>/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on measured.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>code like a girl</title>
      <link>/projects/code-like-a-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/code-like-a-girl/</guid>
      <description>I recently teamed up with code like a girl for a series of Data Storytelling presentations around Australia. Here’s a link list of some of the resources mentioned. The slide presentation also has a lot of links to check out, too.
Data Storytelling resources   name type    tidyverse R metapackage for tidy data  R for Data Science book  RStudio Community forum  Data Storytelling slides  Data Storytelling script github repo  R-Ladies themed slides tutorial  leaflet R package for interactive maps     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>how I organise my thoughts and time</title>
      <link>/projects/thoughts-and-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/thoughts-and-time/</guid>
      <description>my current systems Updated: 2018-11-06
(I wonder if all or some of this should move to the dontpanic readme.)
current tweaks  switch \(\Phi, \theta, \varphi\) after planning \(\cdot\)   pieces  piano practice/task switching/pomodoor bullet journal, used to be as portable as possible blog to see if I’ve made any progress on my study problems for today, to track my productivity system, and to learn about my research problems; in short, blog for me, don’t worry about anyone else: but keep it to those three categories; one category per post, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>measures.</title>
      <link>/projects/measures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/measures/</guid>
      <description>I like Newport’s term deep work.
% -- % -- % -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>news</title>
      <link>/projects/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/events/</guid>
      <description>events in 2018     event date role    Evidence Synthesis Hackathon    La Trobe University Choose Maths day June 4 10 minute speech to school children about the Japanese concept of ikigai and how I find ikigai in practicing mathematical science and a panel session Q &amp;amp; A.  useR! 2018       </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>statistical rethinking</title>
      <link>/projects/statistical-rethinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/statistical-rethinking/</guid>
      <description># packages library(tidyverse) library(patchwork) I’ve joined a bookclub
Chapter Two Practice Easy Question One Which of the expressions below correspond to the statement: the probability of rain on Monday?
P(rain) P(rain|Monday) P(Monday|rain) P(rain,Monday)/P(Monday)  Answer Choices (2) and (4).
I went looking for solutions and came across this,
“the probability of rain on Monday” I think the statement could be interpreted in two different ways. First, the statement might just mean “what is the probability of rain on any given day”.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>