<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Threecsq on measured.</title>
    <link>/tags/threecsq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Threecsq on measured.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/threecsq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>power law distributions</title>
      <link>/2018/07/25/power-law-distributions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/25/power-law-distributions/</guid>
      <description># packages library(tidyverse) draft - is this pushing inadvertently?  what the power law? A functional relationship between two quantities where a relative change in one results in a proportional change in the other. Mathematically, given a relation \(f(x) = ax^{-k}\), \[ f(cx) = a(cx)^{-k} = c^{-k}f(x) \\prop f(x) \]
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>organising my thoughts</title>
      <link>/2018/06/03/organising-my-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/03/organising-my-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>Ever in search of inbox zen, I’m hoping to plough through my daily review today.
I am still failing to finish it. I think I’m falling into the trap of making gcal too complicated and too big a part of my workflow.
I think I’ll try erring towards writing with pen and paper whenever I have a choice.
Often I plan a talk better with pen and paper. I think I think clearer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>so good, so far</title>
      <link>/2018/06/01/so-good-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/01/so-good-so-far/</guid>
      <description>Day two, and I’ve managed to to at least remember to create the .Rmd file and write a sentence.
 Try writing every day and see if it has a measurable positive effect.
 I’m catching the train the numbats today, going to see if I can get more done on the train.
Visited numbats group today to see Hugh Parsonage’s talk. He was visiting from the Grattan institute and he showed us how they were working with R to provide reports on policy and so forth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>