<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on measured.</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on measured.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>simulating meta-analysis data</title>
      <link>/2018/07/26/simulating-meta-analysis-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/26/simulating-meta-analysis-data/</guid>
      <description># packages library(tidyverse) meta-parameters I want to (re)run trials of simulations for:
 different sample sizes different distributions (also different arm adjustment in the meta-analysis simulation)  meta_parameters &amp;lt;- list( sample_size = c(15, 30), distribution = list( list( dist = &amp;quot;exp&amp;quot;, pars = list(rate = 2) ), list( dist = &amp;quot;lnorm&amp;quot;, pars = list(meanlog = 2, sdlog = 1) ) ) ) %&amp;gt;% purrr::cross() # take a look meta_parameters[1:2] %&amp;gt;% str() ## List of 2 ## $ :List of 2 ## .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>power law distributions</title>
      <link>/2018/07/25/power-law-distributions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/25/power-law-distributions/</guid>
      <description># packages library(tidyverse) draft - is this pushing inadvertently?  what the power law? A functional relationship between two quantities where a relative change in one results in a proportional change in the other. Mathematically, given a relation \(f(x) = ax^{-k}\), \[ f(cx) = a(cx)^{-k} = c^{-k}f(x) \\prop f(x) \]
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>if we&#39;re really committed to diversity, crying should be okay</title>
      <link>/2018/07/18/crying-should-be-okay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/18/crying-should-be-okay/</guid>
      <description>I believe that all people struggle with adulting, and that no one is perfect. Although my lifetime has shaped me as noticably different to many people, for the first time in a long while I feel I’ve been able to make use of my strengths.
 never been so proud #choosemaths https://t.co/8gptuDY4Dy — Charles T. Gray (@cantabile) July 16, 2018    I may seem different but, to employ statistical parlance, conditioning on a lifetime of being socially demeaned1, my bias from the point estimate of the expected value approximates zero.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons learnt from balancing technique, gigs, and composing</title>
      <link>/2018/07/06/index-cards-bujo-pomodoros/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/06/index-cards-bujo-pomodoros/</guid>
      <description>## Linking to ImageMagick 6.9.7.4 ## Enabled features: fontconfig, freetype, fftw, lcms, pango, x11 ## Disabled features: cairo, ghostscript, rsvg, webp As a pianist I had daily demands on my time, a surprising mountain of administration faced me. I had gigs to book, rehearsals and lessons to schedule (and forever reschedule, have you worked with parents juggling several children?), but that was just to pay the rent.
The whole point of accepting the crappy conditions and pay was to give myself time to pursue my own musical interests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>testing as debugging</title>
      <link>/2018/07/01/testing-as-debugging/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/01/testing-as-debugging/</guid>
      <description>I’m writing my first tests at the moment.
I’ve been rather enamoured with the idea of testing for about six months now, but haven’t had much of a chance to work on research.
So, I’m finally now sitting down to begin my first package in earnest, and thus writing my first tests. Seeing as I had a request, I thought I’d write my thoughts at this fairly early point. I must confess, however, that this post wandered around a bit and I’m not sure how useful John would find it, alas; it’s not really an explanatory post, more of an exploration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the quack-quack environment</title>
      <link>/2018/06/26/quack-quack-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/26/quack-quack-environment/</guid>
      <description>This post follows on from the post I wrote leading up to the workshop.
What I found myself jonesing for at the workshop last week was an environment called quack-quack that would output coloured pseudocode.
There was much feedback from the workshop last week along the lines of it being great to have more autonomy in the learning process. But I feel without clearer delineation the pseudo code isn’t quite there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>repeating postables</title>
      <link>/2018/06/25/repeating-postables/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/25/repeating-postables/</guid>
      <description>Thoughts on things I might like to revisit. Location and soundtrack, future me always finds interesting.
What I’m listening to The Weakerthans’ Reconstruction Site.
 Where I am Back home at \(3c^2\).
 What is on fire?  Sort out travel varameta R-Curious   The quack quack environment &amp;gt; Tomorrow’s post.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>finally, a use for a pie chart</title>
      <link>/2018/06/18/pie-chart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/18/pie-chart/</guid>
      <description>I’ve switched to using index cards as my main prompt, and my bujo as more of a gtd-style ubiquitous capture device.
I wrote all my daily review actions on</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A coding workshop without code</title>
      <link>/2018/06/17/a-coding-workshop-without-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/17/a-coding-workshop-without-code/</guid>
      <description>I’m currently working on R-Curious, a workshop hosted by R-Ladies.
Something that bothers me about workshop convention is the trap of copy and paste code. I want to develop a system of pseudo code that is easily discernable by newbies. I wonder if something like this already exists?
As a piano teacher, I found it was dramatic how important it was to make sure the student was doing, thinking for themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gitflow for measured.</title>
      <link>/2018/06/12/gitflow-for-measured/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/12/gitflow-for-measured/</guid>
      <description>Had a good chat to the ever helpful Miles about git yesterday. A good follow-up from the unconf where I cornered Jenny and pestered her with questions. I think I’m starting to understand things a bit better.
Anyway, no better place to try things out than the blog, which I assume no one reads :)
create branch git checkout -b &amp;lt;branch-name&amp;gt;1 make changes stage git add . and commit git commit -m &amp;quot;&amp;lt;some-message&amp;gt;&amp;quot; push git push origin &amp;lt;branch-name&amp;gt; merge by pull request on github  So, how to integrate this with a blogging workflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ikigai</title>
      <link>/2018/06/04/ikigai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/04/ikigai/</guid>
      <description>Today, I talk at the AMSI Choose Maths Day at La Trobe.
I’ve been giving a bunch of career-oriented outreach talks about the concept of ikigai, a purpose for being, a reason to get out of bed.
I like to replace do what you’re good at with do what you enjoy getting good at.
Seemed like time to put some slides together. I’m cutting down on the number of bullet points, but I’m not sure I’m ready to go with just visuals, like I saw Kara rock at Seattle RLadies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>organising my thoughts</title>
      <link>/2018/06/03/organising-my-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/03/organising-my-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>Ever in search of inbox zen, I’m hoping to plough through my daily review today.
I am still failing to finish it. I think I’m falling into the trap of making gcal too complicated and too big a part of my workflow.
I think I’ll try erring towards writing with pen and paper whenever I have a choice.
Often I plan a talk better with pen and paper. I think I think clearer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a rest day</title>
      <link>/2018/06/02/a-rest-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/02/a-rest-day/</guid>
      <description>Is it better to work every morning and knock off early? Or is it better to take rest days and work longer during the week? I’m still not sure.
Today is a rest day, and I’m going to colonise Mars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>so good, so far</title>
      <link>/2018/06/01/so-good-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/01/so-good-so-far/</guid>
      <description>Day two, and I’ve managed to to at least remember to create the .Rmd file and write a sentence.
 Try writing every day and see if it has a measurable positive effect.
 I’m catching the train the numbats today, going to see if I can get more done on the train.
Visited numbats group today to see Hugh Parsonage’s talk. He was visiting from the Grattan institute and he showed us how they were working with R to provide reports on policy and so forth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a place to rest my thoughts</title>
      <link>/2018/05/31/a-place-to-rest-my-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/31/a-place-to-rest-my-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve spent any time around me at all, you’ll know that work is a coping mechanism for me.
This blog is less about other people and more about keeping myself grounded through semi-regular posts. I’d say I’d aim for one a day, but honestly, one a month would probably be pushing it.
That being said, I think I’ll try for every day for a little while. So, I guess I should add it to the daily review.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>