<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Productivity on measured.</title>
    <link>/categories/productivity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Productivity on measured.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>repeating postables</title>
      <link>/2018/06/25/repeating-postables/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/25/repeating-postables/</guid>
      <description>Thoughts on things I might like to revisit. Location and soundtrack, future me always finds interesting.
What I’m listening to The Weakerthans’ Reconstruction Site.
 Where I am Back home at \(3c^2\).
 What is on fire?  Sort out travel varameta R-Curious   The quack quack environment &amp;gt; Tomorrow’s post.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>finally, a use for a pie chart</title>
      <link>/2018/06/18/pie-chart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/18/pie-chart/</guid>
      <description>I’ve switched to using index cards as my main prompt, and my bujo as more of a gtd-style ubiquitous capture device.
I wrote all my daily review actions on</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a rest day</title>
      <link>/2018/06/02/a-rest-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/02/a-rest-day/</guid>
      <description>Is it better to work every morning and knock off early? Or is it better to take rest days and work longer during the week? I’m still not sure.
Today is a rest day, and I’m going to colonise Mars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>so good, so far</title>
      <link>/2018/06/01/so-good-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/01/so-good-so-far/</guid>
      <description>Day two, and I’ve managed to to at least remember to create the .Rmd file and write a sentence.
 Try writing every day and see if it has a measurable positive effect.
 I’m catching the train the numbats today, going to see if I can get more done on the train.
Visited numbats group today to see Hugh Parsonage’s talk. He was visiting from the Grattan institute and he showed us how they were working with R to provide reports on policy and so forth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a place to rest my thoughts</title>
      <link>/2018/05/31/a-place-to-rest-my-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/31/a-place-to-rest-my-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve spent any time around me at all, you’ll know that work is a coping mechanism for me.
This blog is less about other people and more about keeping myself grounded through semi-regular posts. I’d say I’d aim for one a day, but honestly, one a month would probably be pushing it.
That being said, I think I’ll try for every day for a little while. So, I guess I should add it to the daily review.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>