<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Productive Research on measured.</title>
    <link>/categories/productive-research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Productive Research on measured.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/productive-research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons learnt from balancing technique, gigs, and composing</title>
      <link>/2018/07/06/index-cards-bujo-pomodoros/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/06/index-cards-bujo-pomodoros/</guid>
      <description>## Linking to ImageMagick 6.9.7.4 ## Enabled features: fontconfig, freetype, fftw, lcms, pango, x11 ## Disabled features: cairo, ghostscript, rsvg, webp As a pianist I had daily demands on my time, a surprising mountain of administration faced me. I had gigs to book, rehearsals and lessons to schedule (and forever reschedule, have you worked with parents juggling several children?), but that was just to pay the rent.
The whole point of accepting the crappy conditions and pay was to give myself time to pursue my own musical interests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>repeating postables</title>
      <link>/2018/06/25/repeating-postables/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/25/repeating-postables/</guid>
      <description>Thoughts on things I might like to revisit. Location and soundtrack, future me always finds interesting.
What I’m listening to The Weakerthans’ Reconstruction Site.
 Where I am Back home at \(3c^2\).
 What is on fire?  Sort out travel varameta R-Curious   The quack quack environment &amp;gt; Tomorrow’s post.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>organising my thoughts</title>
      <link>/2018/06/03/organising-my-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/03/organising-my-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>Ever in search of inbox zen, I’m hoping to plough through my daily review today.
I am still failing to finish it. I think I’m falling into the trap of making gcal too complicated and too big a part of my workflow.
I think I’ll try erring towards writing with pen and paper whenever I have a choice.
Often I plan a talk better with pen and paper. I think I think clearer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>how I organise my thoughts and time</title>
      <link>/projects/thoughts-and-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/thoughts-and-time/</guid>
      <description>my current systems Updated: 2018-10-19
(I wonder if all or some of this should move to the dontpanic readme.)
current tweaks  switch \(\Phi, \theta, \varphi\) after planning \(\cdot\)   pieces  piano practice/task switching/pomodoor bullet journal, used to be as portable as possible blog to see if I’ve made any progress on my study problems for today, to track my productivity system, and to learn about my research problems; in short, blog for me, don’t worry about anyone else: but keep it to those three categories; one category per post, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>